https://laptopwise.com/privacy-policy/

Accessories
Privacy Policy for Laptop WiseAt Laptop Wise, accessible from https://laptopwise.com/, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Laptop Wise and how we use it.If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Laptop Wise. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. ConsentBy using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms. Information we collectThe personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, company name, address, email address, and telephone number.How we use your informationWe use the information we collect in various ways, including to:Provide, operate, and maintain our websiteImprove, personalize, and expand our websiteUnderstand and analyze how you use our websiteDevelop new products, services, features, and functionalityCommunicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposesSend you emailsFind and prevent fraudLog FilesLaptop Wise follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.Our Advertising PartnersSome of advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partners are listed below. Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their policies on user data. For easier access, we hyperlinked to their Privacy Policies below.Googlehttps://policies.google.com/technologies/adsAdvertising Partners Privacy PoliciesYou may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Laptop Wise.Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Laptop Wise, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.Note that Laptop Wise has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.Third Party Privacy PoliciesLaptop Wise’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:Request that a business that collects a consumer’s personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.Request that a business that sells a consumer’s personal data, not sell the consumer’s personal data.If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.GDPR Data Protection RightsWe would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.Children’s InformationAnother part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.Laptop Wise does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
Search for:
Top Picks
Bestseller No. 1
Acer Aspire 5 Slim Laptop, 15.6 inches Full HD IPS Display, AMD Ryzen 3 3200U, Vega 3 Graphics, 4GB DDR4, 128GB SSD, Backlit Keyboard, Windows 10 in S Mode, A515-43-R19L, Silver
$477.98
Buy on Amazon
Bestseller No. 2
2020 Newest HP 15.6 FHD IPS Touchscreen Laptop,10th Gen Intel Quad-Core i5-1035G1 (Up to 3.60GHz, Beat i7-8550U), 16GB RAM, 512GB SSD, Fast Charge, Webcam, HDMI, USB-A&C, WiFi, Win10,w/GM Accessories
$749.00
Buy on Amazon
SaleBestseller No. 3
Lenovo IdeaPad 3 14" Laptop, 14.0" FHD 1920 x 1080 Display, AMD Ryzen 5 3500U Processor, 8GB DDR4 RAM, 256GB SSD, AMD Radeon Vega 8 Graphics, Narrow Bezel, Windows 10, 81W0003QUS, Abyss Blue
$421.53
Buy on Amazon
SaleBestseller No. 4
ASUS TUF Gaming Laptop, 15.6” 144Hz Full HD IPS-Type Display, Intel Core i7-9750H Processor, GeForce GTX 1650, 8GB DDR4, 512GB PCIe SSD, Gigabit Wi-Fi 5, Windows 10 Home, FX505GT-AB73
$804.00
Buy on Amazon
SaleBestseller No. 5
2020 HP 15.6" HD LED Display Laptop, Intel Pentium Gold 6405U Processor, 4GB DDR4 RAM, 128GB SSD, HDMI, Webcam, WI-FI, Windows 10 S, Scarlet Red
$338.21
Buy on Amazon
SaleBestseller No. 6
Evoo 14.1” Ultra Slim Notebook - Elite Series, FHD Display, AMD Ryzen 5 3500U Processor with Radeon Vega 8 Graphics, 8GB RAM, 256GB SSD, HD Webcam, Windows 10 Home, Black (EVC141-12BK)
$449.99
Buy on Amazon
Bestseller No. 7
HP Pavilion x360 14 Convertible 2-in-1 Laptop, 14” Full HD Touchscreen Display, Intel Core i5, 8 GB DDR4 RAM, 512 GB SSD Storage, Windows 10 Home, Backlit Keyboard (14-dh2011nr, 2020 Model)
$738.98
Buy on Amazon
Bestseller No. 8
HP 15-dy1036nr 10th Gen Intel Core i5-1035G1, 15.6-Inch FHD Laptop, Natural Silver
$610.00
Buy on Amazon
SaleBestseller No. 9
Evoo 14.1” Ultra Slim Notebook - Elite Series, FHD Display, AMD Ryzen 5 3500U Processor with Radeon Vega 8 Graphics, 8GB RAM, 256GB SSD, HD Webcam, Windows 10 Home, Silver, EVC141-12SL
$449.99
Buy on Amazon
Bestseller No. 10
HP 15.6-inch HD Laptop, AMD Ryzen 3 3200U Processor, 8 GB RAM, 256 GB SSD, Windows 10 Home (15-ef0021nr, Natural Silver)
$599.66
Buy on Amazon
Search The Site
Search
Facebook
Twitter
Instagram
Youtube
Contact Us
LAPTOPWISE.COM IS A PARTICIPANT IN THE AMAZON SERVICES LLC ASSOCIATES PROGRAM, AN AFFILIATE ADVERTISING PROGRAM DESIGNED TO PROVIDE A MEANS FOR SITES TO EARN ADVERTISING FEES BY ADVERTISING AND LINKING TO AMAZON.COM. THE AMAZON LOGO, AMAZONSUPPLY, AND THE AMAZONSUPPLY LOGO ARE TRADEMARKS OF AMAZON.COM, INC. OR ITS AFFILIATES. AS AN AMAZON ASSOCIATE WE EARN AFFILIATE COMMISSIONS FROM QUALIFYING PURCHASES.
LaptopWise © 2020. All Rights Reserved.
Copy link
Powered by Social Snap
